- Sheldon, I know what I'm doing.
- If you knew what you were doing...
(Sheldon:)...there wouldn't be a space toilet
where my coffee table should be.
(Raj:)Howard, wait.
(Raj:)Why don't you use this instead of the PVC
to keep the filter assembly in place?
(Howard:)Because this is not a spare part
from the space station.
(Howard:)This is the thing from the pizza box
that keeps the lid from touching the cheese.
Is that what that's for?
In India, the lid just touches the cheese.
(Raj:)We also have rampant poverty
and periodic outbreaks of cholera...
(Raj:)...so a little cardboard in our cheese
is no biggie.
- Where you going?
- Comic-book store.
(Sheldon:)Oh, an excellent idea.
I could certainly use a break.
- Me too.
- You can go to the comic book store...
(Howard:)...when man can once again
safely poop in space.
(Sheldon:)Why does Leonard get to go?
Because he's upset
over his situation with Penny.
(Leonard:)And if I have to hear about it again,
I'm gonna kick him in his ovaries.
- Thanks for understanding, Howard.
HOWARD: I got your back, sister.
(Howard:)All right, I think we've got a prototype
ready to test. Hand me that Tupperware.